<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>A Filipino Geek. Developer</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 04:28:05 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 04:28:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Switched to AMP!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Before I switched to AMP - First, I lost my GitHub account because I installed MIUI on my phone and forgot to backup
my Google Authenticator, for my two-factor auth. Second, as you may have noticed, I also switched to GitLab Pages and to my surprise,
GitLab has unlimited private repositories for free, and boom, sold. Third, I fixed some stupid yet serious 
grammatical errors and damn, that was really stupid of me. And lastly, there, I finally switched to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ampproject.org/&quot;&gt;AMP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMP or Accelerated Mobile Pages is, as their site says:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;a way to build web pages for static content that render fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it’s superb. Plus your site gets to have a proper seat on Google’s first page, given that you have quite a number of readers.
Since I only post text, images and mostly basic stuff, my home page loads for about a second and my other pages, a little bit less than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To finish off my AMP switch, I also added an AMP compatible Disqus comments. I had a small wrinkle implementing one: it required
the universal code to be hosted on a different domain, and I don’t have one! I leech on free stuff.
Luckily, a guy named &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jamestomasino&quot;&gt;James Tomasino&lt;/a&gt; hosted one and made it publicly available. Seriously, what a guy.
If you’re like me, then this one’s for you: &lt;a href=&quot;https://labs.tomasino.org/disqus-in-amp/&quot;&gt;Peekaboo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll write a How-To on implementing AMP to your Jekyll website. Using, of course, James’ universal code. So tune in.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 16:16:01 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/misc/2017/01/30/switched-to-amp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/misc/2017/01/30/switched-to-amp.html</guid>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
        
        <category>misc</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emgu CV Face Detection App for WPF</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lately, I’ve been playing around with Emgu CV’s face detection features and it works really well. As I am fond
developing apps for the WPF platform, I made one for it too. I’ll try to update this one from time to time,
but please take note that the purpose of this app is to be a “base” app for your Face Detection needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, the app has few number of features, here they are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clean Material Design UI&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SQLite Database&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to &lt;strong&gt;Add User&lt;/strong&gt; with Name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to &lt;strong&gt;Take Logs&lt;/strong&gt; with Date and Time&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to &lt;strong&gt;Show All Logs&lt;/strong&gt; in a list&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to filter all logs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And written in &lt;strong&gt;MVVM Pattern&lt;/strong&gt; for scalability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just download the source, fire up the solution and you’re good. I’ll be adding the ability to edit users in
the future and view the user’s face on the Logs Tab. Meanwhile, take a look at the source on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zxcdani/EmguFaceDetectionWPF&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 16:16:01 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/2016/07/08/emgu-face-detection-for-wpf.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/2016/07/08/emgu-face-detection-for-wpf.html</guid>
        
        <category>wpf</category>
        
        <category>emgu</category>
        
        <category>c#</category>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
